

bikram thapa

Address: butwal Phone: 9849807289

Email: bikramthapa37@gmail.com Date of Birth: April 18, 1991

Objective

I Wanted to build my career as a full stack engineer and currently I working as Web UI/UX designer and increasing expertise in designing and coding skills, which I think is the first step to achieve my goal and planning to jump in frontend developing.

Work Experience

December, 2020 - Now

Senior Web Designer

Webhouse Nepal Pulchowk Lalitpur

Working As Senior Website Designer and My task is to Create and convert PSD or XD mockup into HTML /CSS/JS file and design Facebook post, Brand Designing and Graphic content for website and customer user, besides I was assigned to guide junior designer and interns.

December, 2018 - April, 2019

Senior Web Designer

Radient Infotech Nepal GauriDhara Kathmandu

Worked As Senior Website Designer and My task was Create and convert PSD or XD mockup into HTML /CSS/JS file and design Facebook post and Graphic content for website and customer user, besides I was assigned to guide junior designer and interns.

September, 2018 - December, 2020

Senior Web Desinger

Dradtech Technology Pvt. Ltd

Butwal

Worked As Senior UI/UX Designer and My task was Create and convert PSD or XD mockup into HTML /CSS/JS file and design Facebook post and Graphic content for website and customer user, besides I was assigned to guide junior designer and interns.

December, 2017 -September, 2018

Junior Web Designer

Bitsbeat IT Solution

Baneshwore

Worked As Junior Website Designer my task was convert PSD or XD mockup into HTML /CSS/JS file and design Facebook post and Graphic content for website and customer user.

Education

(Bachelor) - Bsc. Csit 50%

April, 2012 Prime College, Tribhuvan University

Training/Certificates

July, 2013 (4 Months)

Website Designing Broadway Infosys

Job Preference

Looking for: Senior Level Job Categories: IT & Telecommunication Available for: Full Time

Expected Salary: (Above) NRs 40,000.00 (Monthly)

Specializations and Skills

Specializations

Ui/Ux And Mock Up Deisgning

Skills

Web Design, Graphic Design

Personal Information

Gender: Male

Current Address: butwal

Permanent Address: butwal-13 rupandehi

Marital Status: Married

Religion: Buddhism

Nationality: Nepali

Generated By

